Guide to the Antiquarian bookseller catalog collection.
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- C
  - X346 C3835, 1966 - 1977; nos. 136-175, 16 catalogs
    - The Charterhouse of Parma; Parma, Ohio (Box 293, Folder 1810-1811)
    - The Charterhouse of Parma; Parma, Ohio (Box 294, Folder 1812-1813)
  - X346 C39, 1871-undated; nos. 6-30, 31 catalogs
    Includes some unnumbered catalogs and supplements
    - Charles C. Chatfield Co.; New Haven, Conn. (Box 294, Folder 1814-1817)
    - Charles C. Chatfield Co.; New Haven, Conn. (Box 295, Folder 1818-1819)
  - X346 C3958, undated; nos. 4-59, 19 catalogs
    - Leslie Chaundy; London (Box 295, Folder 1820-1823)
  - X346 C3958 I, undated; unnumbered, 4 catalogs
    - Leslie Chaundy Co.; London (Box 295, Folder 1824)
  - X346 C4245, undated; nos. 1-2, 2 catalogs
    - Cheshire Book Shop; Walpole, New Hampshire (Box 295, Folder 1825)
  - X346 C448, 1951 - 1957; nos. 1-26, 13 catalogs
    - W. A. Chislett; Oxford (Box 295, Folder 1826-1828)
  - X346 C459, 1908-undated; nos. 1-142, 94 catalogs
    Name variant: Pierre Chrétien
    - George Chrétien; Paris (Box 296, Folder 1829-1838)
    - George Chrétien; Paris (Box 297, Folder 1839-1842)
  - X346 C46, 1984; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - Christie, Manson, Woods LTD.; London (Box 297, Folder 1843)
  - X346 C4625, undated; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - Niels Christensen; Bloomfield, New Jersey (Box 297, Folder 1844)
  - X346 C54, 1903-undated; nos. 3-700, 259 catalogs
    - Arthur H. Clark; Cleveland, Ohio (Box 297, Folder 1845-1846)
    - Arthur H. Clark; Cleveland, Ohio (Box 298, Folder 1847-1852)
    - Arthur H. Clark; Cleveland, Ohio (Box 299, Folder 1853-1857)
    - Arthur H. Clark; Cleveland, Ohio (Box 300, Folder 1858-1861)
    - Arthur H. Clark; Cleveland, Ohio (Box 301, Folder 1862-1871)
    - Arthur H. Clark; Cleveland, Ohio (Box 302, Folder 1872-1881)
    - Arthur H. Clark; Cleveland, Ohio (Box 303, Folder 1882-1891)
    - Arthur H. Clark; Cleveland, Ohio (Box 304, Folder 1892-1894)
  - X346 C54 II, undated; unnumbered, nos. S1303- S5087, A62- A179, 21 catalogs
    - Arthur H. Clark; Cleveland, Ohio (Box 304, Folder 1895-1899)
  - X346 C547, undated; nos. 23-67, unnumbered supplements, 40 catalogs
    - A. S. Clark; Peekskill, N. Y. (Box 304, Folder 1900-1901)
    - A. S. Clark; Peekskill, N. Y. (Box 305, Folder 1902-1905)
  - X346 C5477, 1920; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - Francis Clarke; London (Box 305, Folder 1906)
  - X346 C552, undated; nos. 7-30, 5 catalogs
    - J. Clarke-Hall Ltd; London (Box 305, Folder 1907-1908)
  - X346 C558, 1811; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - W. Clarke and Sons; London (Box 305, Folder 1909)
  - X346 C578, 1905 - 1908; nos. 1-6, nos. 1-10, 13 catalogs
    - C. Clavreuil; Paris (Box 305, Folder 1910-1912)
  - X346 C578 II, 1919 - 1936; nos. 2-114, 85 catalogs
    - C. Clavreuil; Paris (Box 305, Folder 1913-1914)
    - C. Clavreuil; Paris (Box 306, Folder 1915-1922)
  - X346 C578 III, 1952 - 1955; nos. 39-46, 6 catalogs
    - C. Clavreuil; Paris (Box 306, Folder 1923-1924)
  - X346 C628, 1953 - 1965; nos. 1-19, 18 catalogs
    - Alec Clunes; London (Box 306, Folder 1925-1926)
    - Alec Clunes; London (Box 307, Folder 1927)
  - X346 C63, 1871; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - Jones Cobb Co.; California (Box 307, Folder 1928)
  - X346 C6604, undated; nos. 8-92, 13 catalogs
    - Chiswick Book Shop; New York (Box 307, Folder 1929-1931)
  - X346 C6604 I, undated; nos. 2-50, 32 catalogs
    - Chiswick Book Shop; New York (Box 307, Folder 1932-1934)
  - X346 C662, undated, 1876-1902; nos. 23-224, 63 catalogs
    - Albert Cohn; Berlin (Box 307, Folder 1935-1938)
    - Albert Cohn; Berlin (Box 308, Folder 1939-1948)
    - Albert Cohn; Berlin (Box 309, Folder 1949-1950)
  - X346 C6621, undated; unnumbered, 2 catalogs
    - B. F. Cohn; New York City (Box 309, Folder 1951)
  - X346 C6695, 1951 - 1958; nos. 16-97, 44 catalogs
    - Pierre Colas; Paris (Box 309, Folder 1952-1958)
  - X346 C68, 1889 - 1986; nos. 18-911, 179 catalogs
    - The Collector; New York (Box 309, Folder 1959-1960)
    - The Collector; New York (Box 310, Folder 1961-1969)
    - The Collector; New York (Box 311, Folder 1970-1975)
  - X346 C6855, undated, 1937-1941; nos. 1-12, 5 catalogs
    - Collectors' Bookshop; New York (Box 311, Folder 1976-1977)
  - X346 C692, 1814; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - Collins's Catalogue; London (Box 311, Folder 1978)
  - X346 C71, 1825 - 1829; unnumbered, 2 catalogs
    - William A. Colman; New York (Box 311, Folder 1979)
  - X346 C717, undated, 1942[?]; unnumbered, 9 catalogs
    - Colonial Book Service; New York, N. Y. (Box 312, Folder 1980)
  - X346 C729, 1916 - 1957; nos. 2-50, 49 catalogs
    - Combridges; Sussex, England (Box 312, Folder 1981-1989)
  - X346 C73, 1889-1962, undated; nos. 54-678, 578 catalogs
    - James G. Commin; Exeter (Box 313, Folder 1900-1909)
    - James G. Commin; Exeter (Box 314, Folder 1910-1918)
    - James G. Commin; Exeter (Box 315, Folder 1919-1928)
    - James G. Commin; Exeter (Box 316, Folder 1929-1937)
    - James G. Commin; Exeter (Box 317, Folder 1938-1947)
    - James G. Commin; Exeter (Box 318, Folder 1948-1958)
    - James G. Commin; Exeter (Box 319, Folder 1959-1968)
    - James G. Commin; Exeter (Box 320, Folder 1969-1978)
    - James G. Commin; Exeter (Box 321, Folder 1979-1987)
  - X346 C735, 1898 - 1959; nos. 32-149, 44 catalogs
    - Horace G. Commin; Bournemouth (Box 321, Folder 1988)
    - Horace G. Commin; Bournemouth (Box 322, Folder 1989-1995)
  - X346 C735 I, undated; nos. 7-60, 21 catalogs
    - Horace G. Commin; Bournemouth (Box 322, Folder 1996-1998)
    - Horace G. Commin; Bournemouth (Box 323, Folder 1999-2002)
  - X346 C754, undated; no. 5, 1 catalog
    - Richard M. Condon; Surrey, England (Box 323, Folder 2003)
  - X346 C758, undated; nos. 9-54, 9 catalogs
    - Conestoga Book Service; Pasadena, California (Box 323, Folder 2004-2005)
  - X346 C7681, undated; nos. 3-19, 14 catalogs
    - Continental Book Company; Atlanta, Georgia (Box 323, Folder 2006-2009)
  - X346 C7681 I, undated-1947; nos. 4-6, 11 catalogs
    - Continental Book Company; Atlanta, Georgia (Box 324, Folder 2010-2012)
  - X346 C774, 1818; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - Cooke and Hale; Hartford (Box 324, Folder 2013)
  - X346 C777, 1849 - 1850; unnumbered, 3 catalogs
    - Cooley and Keese; New York (Box 324, Folder 2014-2015)
  - X346 C8165, undated; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - J. E. Cornish; Mancester (Box 324, Folder 2016)
  - X346 C8169, undated, 1938-1939; nos. 3-6, 4 catalogs
    - J. S. Cornwall; Berks, England (Box 324, Folder 2017)
  - X346 C817, undated; unnumbered, 35 catalogs
    - The Luther M. Cornwall Co.; New York, N. Y. (Box 324, Folder 2018-2020)
    - The Luther M. Cornwall Co.; New York, N. Y. (Box 325, Folder 2021)
  - X346 C8175, 1946; no. 473, 1 catalog
    - Coronet Book Shop; New Orleans, LA. (Box 325, Folder 2022)
  - X346 C8176, 1938; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - Cortez Gallaries; New York City (Box 325, Folder 2023)
  - X346 C819, 1948; no. G 2/48, 1 catalog
    - Corvinus Bookshop; Bristol, England (Box 325, Folder 2024)
  - X346 C821, 1941-undated; Letter + nos.4-26, 30 catalogs
    - Cosmopolitan Science and Art Service Company, Inc.; New York, New York (Box 325, Folder 2025-2032)
    - Cosmopolitan Science and Art Service Company, Inc.; New York, New York (Box 326, Folder 2033-2034)
  - X346 C8275, 1963 - 1967; nos. 1-3, 3 catalogs
    - André Cottet; Genève (Box 326, Folder 2035)
  - X346 C8275 I, 1964 - 1970; nos.1-5, 3 catalogs
    - André Cottet; Genève (Box 326, Folder 2036)
  - X346 C838, undated; nos. 1-50, 5 catalogs
    - Covent Garden Bookshop; London (Box 326, Folder 2037-2038)
  - X346 C8385, undated; nos. 1-9, 8 catalogs
    - Nathaniel Cowen; Saugerties, N. Y. (Box 326, Folder 2039-2041)
  - X346 C839, undated-1981; nos. 40-50, 7 catalogs
    - Ian H. R. Cowley; Nottingham, England (Box 327, Folder 2042-2043)
  - X346 C8395, 1950 - 1953; unnumbered, 9 catalogs
    - J. Stevens Cox; Ilchester, England (Box 327, Folder 2044-2046)
  - X346 C8395 I, 1953 - 1966; unnumbered, 55 catalogs
    - J. Stevens Cox; Ilchester, England (Box 327, Folder 2047-2053)
    - J. Stevens Cox; Ilchester, England (Box 328, Folder 2054-2055)
  - X346 C842, 1915 - 1984; nos. 1-149, 83 catalogs
    - Craddock Barnard; Tunbridge Wells, England (Box 328, Folder 2056-2062)
    - Craddock Barnard; Tunbridge Wells, England (Box 329, Folder 2063-2072)
    - Craddock Barnard; Tunbridge Wells, England (Box 330, Folder 2073-2074)
  - X346 C86, 1932 - 1960; nos. 14-47 + unnumbered, 33 catalogs
    - Creasser's Book and Print Shop; Toronto, Canada (Box 330, Folder 2075-2080)
  - X346 C8675, undated; nos. 32-37, 4 catalogs
    - Creyghton; The Netherlands (Box 330, Folder 2081-2082)
  - X346 C882, 1683; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - William Crooke; London (Box 330, Folder 2083)
  - X346 C8863, 1929 - 1933; unnumbered, 3 catalogs
    - Stanley Crowe; London (Box 331, Folder 2084)
  - X346 C8863 II, undated; nos. 20-89, 29 catalogs
    - Stanley Crowe; London (Box 331, Folder 2085-2091)
  - X346 C8864, 1964-1968, undated; unnumbered, 9 catalogs
    - Thomas Crowe; Norfolk (Box 331, Folder 2092-2093)
  - X346 C8864 I, 1964 - 1978; nos. 122-154, 13 catalogs
    - Thomas Crowe; Norfolk (Box 331, Folder 2094)
    - Thomas Crowe; Norfolk (Box 332, Folder 2095-2097)
  - X346 C93, 1914 - 1922; unnumbered, 2 catalogs
    - Edward Curtis; San Francisco, California (Box 332, Folder 2098)
  - X346 C9361, undated; nos. 3-69, 50 catalogs
    - The Current Company; Bristol, Rhode Island (Box 332, Folder 2099-2104)
    - The Current Company; Bristol, Rhode Island (Box 333, Folder 2105-2113)
    - The Current Company; Bristol, Rhode Island (Box 334, Folder 2114-2116)
  - X346 C9361 I, undated; unnumbered, 4 catalogs
    - The Current Company; Bristol, Rhode Island (Box 334, Folder 2117)
  - X346 C9363, 1968 - 1974; nos. 3-29, 7 catalogs
    - L. W. Currey; Mattapan, Mass. (Box 334, Folder 2118-2120)
  - X346 C94, 1911 - 1929; unnumbered, 17 catalogs
    - H. Taylor Curtis; San Francisco (Box 334, Folder 2121-2124)
  - X346 C96, 1815 - 1822; unnumbered, 3 catalogs
    - John Cuthell; London (Box 335, Folder 2125-2126)
  - X346 C972, 1822; unnumbered, 2 catalogs
    - John Cuthell; London (Box 335, Folder 2127)
- D
  - X346 D1185, 1949-1950; unnumbered, 2 catalogs
    - Libraria Sa Da Costa; Lisboa, Portugal (Box 336, Folder 2128-2129)
  - X346 D141, undated; nos. 3-44, 19 catalogs
    - William Victoria Dailey; Los Angeles, California (Box 336, Folder 2130-2137)
  - X346 D1675, undated; nos. 12-103, 25 catalogs
    - James Dally; Hobart, Australia (Box 337, Folder 2138-2145)
    - James Dally; Hobart, Australia (Box 338, Folder 2146-2148)
  - X346 D181, 1928-1966; nos. 2-299, 75 catalogs
    - Maurice Dambournet; Paris (Box 338, Folder 2149-2153)
    - Maurice Dambournet; Paris (Box 339, Folder 2154-2158)
  - X346 D183, 1889-1892, undated; unnumbered, nos. 10-90, 19 catalogs
    - Felix L. Dames; Berlin (Box 339, Folder 2159-2162)
  - X346 D186, 1904-1984; nos. 37-639, 63 catalogs
    - Damm Søn; Oslo (Box 339, Folder 2163-2164)
    - Damm Søn; Oslo (Box 340, Folder 2165-2173)
    - Damm Søn; Oslo (Box 341, Folder 2174-2178)
  - X346 D195, 1951-1967; unnumbered, 12 catalogs
    - The Dance Mart; New York, New York (Box 341, Folder 2179-2180)
  - X346 D225, undated; nos. 16-35, 6 catalogs
    - Price Daniel, Jr.; Waco, Texas (Box 341, Folder 2181)
  - X346 D2275, 1894-1909; unnumbered, 14 catalogs
    - Walter V. Daniell; London (Box 341, Folder 2182-2184)
  - X346 D2275 II, undated; nos. 5-20, 8 catalogs
    - Walter V. Daniell; London (Box 342, Folder 2185-2188)
  - X346 D228, 1847; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - Daniels Smith; Philadelphia (Box 342, Folder 2189)
  - X346 D2285, 1919-1940; nos. 1-45, 51 catalogs
    - Henry Danielson; London (Box 342, Folder 2190-2195)
    - Henry Danielson; London (Box 343, Folder 2196-2205)
  - X346 D237, undated; nos. 15-34, 17 catalogs
    - Munroe d'Antignac; Griffin, Georgia (Box 344, Folder 2206-2208)
  - X346 D241, 1889-1911; unnumbered, 21 catalogs
    - H. Daragon; Paris (Box 344, Folder 2209-2211)
  - X346 D241 II, 1908-1931; nos. 2-24, 14 catalogs
    - H. Daragon; Paris (Box 344, Folder 2212-2214)
  - X346 D244, 1814; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - J. Darcy; London (Box 344, Folder 2215)
  - X346 D2555, undated; no. 17, 1 catalog
    - John C. Daub; Pittsburgh, P.A. (Box 344, Folder 2216)
  - X346 D26, 1924-1976; nos. 4-693, 624 catalogs
    - Dauber and Pine Bookshop, Inc.; New York, N. Y. (Box 344, Folder 2217-2218)
    - Dauber and Pine Bookshop, Inc.; New York, N. Y. (Box 345, Folder 2219-2224)
    - Dauber and Pine Bookshop, Inc.; New York, N. Y. (Box 346, Folder 2225-2229)
    - Dauber and Pine Bookshop, Inc.; New York, N. Y. (Box 347, Folder 2230-2235)
    - Dauber and Pine Bookshop, Inc.; New York, N. Y. (Box 348, Folder 2236-2245)
    - Dauber and Pine Bookshop, Inc.; New York, N. Y. (Box 349, Folder 2246-2255)
    - Dauber and Pine Bookshop, Inc.; New York, N. Y. (Box 350, Folder 2256-2266)
    - Dauber and Pine Bookshop, Inc.; New York, N. Y. (Box 351, Folder 2267-2277)
    - Dauber and Pine Bookshop, Inc.; New York, N. Y. (Box 352, Folder 2278-2289)
    - Dauber and Pine Bookshop, Inc.; New York, N. Y. (Box 353, Folder 2290-2301)
    - Dauber and Pine Bookshop, Inc.; New York, N. Y. (Box 354, Folder 2302-2311)
    - Dauber and Pine Bookshop, Inc.; New York, N. Y. (Box 355, Folder 2312-2321)
    - Dauber and Pine Bookshop, Inc.; New York, N. Y. (Box 356, Folder 2322-2323)
  - X346 D2635, 1962-1965; nos. 1-8, 8 catalogs
    - M. Dauber Bookseller; New York, N. Y. (Box 356, Folder 2324-2325)
  - X346 D265, 1924-1963; nos. 23- 105, 70 catalogs
    - Henri Dauthon; Paris (Box 356, Folder 2326-2333)
    - Henri Dauthon; Paris (Box 357, Folder 2334-2338)
  - X346 D266, 1953-1967; nos. 1-18, 4 catalogs
    - M. D'Auria; Napoli, Italia (Box 357, Folder 2339-2340)
  - X346 D27, 1924-1938; nos. 1-21, 27 catalogs
    - The Davenant Bookshop; Oxford (Box 357, Folder 2341-2344)
  - X346 D28 II, undated; nos. 1-21, 19 catalogs
    - G. David; Cambridge, England (Box 357, Folder 2345)
    - G. David; Cambridge, England (Box 358, Folder 2346-2347)
  - X346 D281, undated; nos. 1-8, 8 catalogs
    - Alexander Davidson, Jr.; New York, N. Y. (Box 358, Folder 2348-2349)
  - X346 D281 II, undated?; nos. 1-23, 16 catalogs
    - Alexander Davidson, Jr.; New York, N. Y. (Box 358, Folder 2350-2351)
  - X346 D281 III, undated?; nos. 26-61, 24 catalogs
    - Alexander Davidson, Jr.; New York, N. Y. (Box 358, Folder 2352-2354)
  - X346 D282, undated; no. 1, 1 catalog
    - Edward A. Davidson; Brooklyn, N. Y. (Box 358, Folder 2355)
  - X346 D2886, undated; nos. 61-325, 117 catalogs
    - Owen Davies; Chicago, Illinois (Box 359, Folder 2356-2365)
    - Owen Davies; Chicago, Illinois (Box 360, Folder 2366-2371)
  - X346 D29 I, 1894, 1913-undated; nos. 1-170, 161 catalogs
    - Davis Orioli; Florence, Italy (Box 360, Folder 2372-2375)
    - Davis Orioli; Florence, Italy (Box 361, Folder 2376-2385)
    - Davis Orioli; Florence, Italy (Box 362, Folder 2386-2395)
    - Davis Orioli; Florence, Italy (Box 363, Folder 2396-2404)
  - X346 D29 II, undated; nos. 1-40, 34 catalogs
    - Davis Orioli; Florence, Italy (Box 363, Folder 2405)
    - Davis Orioli; Florence, Italy (Box 364, Folder 2406-2408)
  - X346 D29 III, 1911-1931; nos. 1-28, 25 catalogs
    - Davis Orioli; Florence, Italy (Box 364, Folder 2409-2413)
  - X346 D29 IV, undated; nos. 2-8, 8 catalogs
    - Davis Orioli; Florence, Italy (Box 364, Folder 2414-2415)
  - X346 D29 V, undated; nos. 1-3, 2 catalogs
    - Davis Orioli; Florence, Italy (Box 365, Folder 2416)
  - X346 D297, 1876; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - R. D. W. Davis Co.; 211 Pine Street [San Francisco?] (Box 365, Folder 2417)
  - X346 D31, undated; nos. 1-472, 26 catalogs
    - William Dawson Sons; London (Box 365, Folder 2418-2426)
  - X346 D31 II, 1929-1982; nos. 1-287, 251 catalogs
    - William Dawson Sons; London (Box 366, Folder 2427-2436)
    - William Dawson Sons; London (Box 367, Folder 2437-2446)
    - William Dawson Sons; London (Box 368, Folder 2447-2455)
    - William Dawson Sons; London (Box 369, Folder 2456-2465)
    - William Dawson Sons; London (Box 370, Folder 2466-2474)
    - William Dawson Sons; London (Box 371, Folder 2475-2482)
    - William Dawson Sons; London (Box 372, Folder 2483-2490)
    - William Dawson Sons; London (Box 373, Folder 2491-2498)
    - William Dawson Sons; London (Box 374, Folder 2499-2504)
    - William Dawson Sons; London (Box 375, Folder 2505-2508)
  - X346 D31 III, undated-1979; nos. 1-454, 20 catalogs
    - William Dawson Sons; London (Box 375, Folder 2509-2510)
    - William Dawson Sons; London (Box 376, Folder 2511-2514)
  - X346 D31 VI, 1952-1978; nos. 1-268, 51 catalogs
    - William Dawson Sons; London (Box 376, Folder 2515-2517)
    - William Dawson Sons; London (Box 377, Folder 2518-2525)
    - William Dawson Sons; London (Box 378, Folder 2526-2527)
  - X346 D32, undated, 1925-1931; unnumbered, 17 catalogs
    - Dawson's Book Shop; Los Angeles, California (Box 378, Folder 2528-2529)
  - X346 D32 I, 1932-1985; nos. 35-485, 337 catalogs
    - Dawson's Book Shop; Los Angeles, California (Box 378, Folder 2530-2532)
    - Dawson's Book Shop; Los Angeles, California (Box 379, Folder 2533-2539)
    - Dawson's Book Shop; Los Angeles, California (Box 380, Folder 2540-2546)
    - Dawson's Book Shop; Los Angeles, California (Box 381, Folder 2547-2553)
    - Dawson's Book Shop; Los Angeles, California (Box 382, Folder 2554-2560)
    - Dawson's Book Shop; Los Angeles, California (Box 383, Folder 2561-2566)
    - Dawson's Book Shop; Los Angeles, California (Box 384, Folder 2567-2573)
    - Dawson's Book Shop; Los Angeles, California (Box 385, Folder 2574)
  - X346 D32 II, 1932-1950; nos. 9-89, 47 catalogs
    - Dawson's Book Shop; Los Angeles, California (Box 385, Folder 2574-2576)
  - X346 D33, 1905-1939; unnumbered, 133 catalogs
    - Day's Library, Ltd.; London (Box 385, Folder 2577-2580)
    - Day's Library, Ltd.; London (Box 386, Folder 2581-2587)
    - Day's Library, Ltd.; London (Box 387, Folder 2588-2590)
  - X346 D33 I, 1951-1952, undated; unnumbered, 8 catalogs
    - Day's Library, Ltd.; London (Box 387, Folder 2591)
  - X346 D356, 1924-1935; nos. 13-49, 16 catalogs
    - Librairie Dechenne, S. A.; Bruxelles (Box 387, Folder 2592-2593)
  - X346 D3576, 1936-1968; nos. 1-58, 50 catalogs
    - Peter Decker; New York City (Box 387, Folder 2594)
    - Peter Decker; New York City (Box 388, Folder 2595-2601)
    - Peter Decker; New York City (Box 389, Folder 2602)
  - X346 D362, 1942-1949; nos. 12-39, 15 catalogs
    - De Forest Book; New Orleans (Box 389, Folder 2603)
  - X346 D365, 1929-1960; nos. 9-61, 49 catalogs
    - Victor Degrange; Paris (Box 389, Folder 2604-2608)
  - X346 D368, undated; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - Deighton, Bell Co.; Cambridge, England (Box 390, Folder 2609)
  - X346 D368 II, 1933-1984; nos. 49-228, 121 catalogs
    - Deighton, Bell Co.; Cambridge, England (Box 390, Folder 2610-2615)
    - Deighton, Bell Co.; Cambridge, England (Box 391, Folder 2616-2621)
    - Deighton, Bell Co.; Cambridge, England (Box 392, Folder 2622-2627)
    - Deighton, Bell Co.; Cambridge, England (Box 393, Folder 2628-2632)
  - X346 D368 III, 1956-1964; nos. 1-23, 17 catalogs
    - Deighton, Bell Co.; Cambridge, England (Box 393, Folder 2633-2634)
  - X346 D368 IV, undated; nos. 3-135, 11 catalogs
    - Deighton, Bell Co.; Cambridge, England (Box 394, Folder 2635-2636)
  - X346 D368 V, 1946-1947; unnumbered, 7 catalogs
    - Deighton, Bell Co.; Cambridge, England (Box 394, Folder 2637)
  - X346 D3681, 1816; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - J. Deighton and Sons; Cambridge (Box 394, Folder 2638)
  - X346 D45, 1929-1940; nos. 30-124, 82 catalogs
    - André Deruelle; Paris (Box 394, Folder 2639-2641)
    - André Deruelle; Paris (Box 395, Folder 2642-2645)
  - X346 D475, undated; nos. 2-211, 22 catalogs
    - Librairie De A. Detaille; Paris (Box 395, Folder 2646)
  - X346 D48, 1922-1939; nos. 40-123, 33 catalogs
    - Albert De Tavernier; Anvers (Box 395, Folder 2647-2648)
  - X346 D481, 1913-1953; nos. 70-358, 141 catalogs
    - A. De Tavernier; Gand (Box 396, Folder 2649-2655)
    - A. De Tavernier; Gand (Box 397, Folder 2656-2659)
  - X346 D4815, 1961, undated; nos. 5-11, 3 catalogs
    - Dethorey's Antikvariat AB; Stockholm (Box 397, Folder 2660)
  - X346 D4882, undated, 1906-1965; nos. 33-159, 34 catalogs
    - Franz Deuticke; Schottenhof (Box 397, Folder 2661-2662)
    - Franz Deuticke; Schottenhof (Box 398, Folder 2663-2665)
  - X346 D489, 1931-1964; nos. 4-138, 18 catalogs
    - Deutsche Buch-Club; Hamburg (Box 398, Folder 2666-2669)
    - Deutsche Buch-Club; Hamburg (Box 399, Folder 2670)
  - X346 D489 II, 1936-1973; unnumbered, 21 catalogs
    - Deutsche Buch-Club; Hamburg (Box 399, Folder 2671-2673)
  - X346 D4897, undated; nos. 5-27, 8 catalogs
    - Deutsche Buch-Export und Import; Leipzig (Box 399, Folder 2674-2676)
    - Deutsche Buch-Export und Import; Leipzig (Box 400, Folder 2677)
  - X346 D498, undated-1925; nos. 1-25, 10 catalogs
    - R. W. P. De Vries; Amsterdam (Box 400, Folder 2678-2680)
  - X346 D498 I, undated, 1902-1909; unnumbered, 6 catalogs
    - R. W. P. De Vries; Amsterdam (Box 400, Folder 2681-2682)
  - X346 D56, 1889-1947; nos. 87-494, 189 catalogs
    - Richard D. Dickinson; London (Box 401, Folder 2683-2689)
    - Richard D. Dickinson; London (Box 402, Folder 2690-2695)
    - Richard D. Dickinson; London (Box 403, Folder 2696-2702)
    - Richard D. Dickinson; London (Box 404, Folder 2703-2707)
  - X346 D565, 1826; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - Firmin Didot; Paris (Box 404, Folder 2708)
  - X346 D5666, 1935-1937; unnumbered, 2 catalogs
    - Dieterich'sche Verlagsbuchhandlung; Leipzig (Box 404, Folder 2709)
  - X346 D5692, undated; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - Basil Dighton; London (Box 404, Folder 2710)
  - X346 D6155, 1962-1968; nos. 2-5, 3 catalogs
    - J. H. Dingwall; London (Box 405, Folder 2711)
  - X346 D6428, 1946-1953; nos. 1-15, 15 catalogs
    - Arthur Dobell; London (Box 405, Folder 2712)
  - X346 D65, 1911-1930; unnumbered, 12 catalogs
    - Bertram Dobell; London (Box 405, Folder 2713-2714)
  - X346 D65 I, 1878-1946; nos. 6-461, 299 catalogs
    - Bertram Dobell; London (Box 405, Folder 2715-2717)
    - Bertram Dobell; London (Box 406, Folder 2718-2724)
    - Bertram Dobell; London (Box 407, Folder 2725-2731)
    - Bertram Dobell; London (Box 408, Folder 2732-2737)
    - Bertram Dobell; London (Box 409, Folder 2738-2743)
  - X346 D65 II, 1921-1934; nos. 1-139, 138 catalogs
    Name variant: P. J. & A. E. Dobell; London
    - Bertram Dobell; London (Box 409, Folder 2744)
    - Bertram Dobell; London (Box 410, Folder 2745-2751)
    - Bertram Dobell; London (Box 411, Folder 2752-2758)
  - X346 D654, 1933-1971; nos. 1-185, 190 catalogs
    - Dobell's Antiquarian Bookstore; Kent, England (Box 411, Folder 2759)
    - Dobell's Antiquarian Bookstore; Kent, England (Box 412, Folder 2760-2765)
    - Dobell's Antiquarian Bookstore; Kent, England (Box 413, Folder 2766-2772)
    - Dobell's Antiquarian Bookstore; Kent, England (Box 414, Folder 2773-2775)
  - X346 D6545, undated; unnumbered, 15 catalogs
    - Dobie's Book Shop; San Marcos, Texas (Box 414, Folder 2776)
  - X346 D6545 I, undated; nos. 1-2, 2 catalogs
    - Dudley R. Dobie; San Marcos, Texas (Box 414, Folder 2777)
  - X346 D6573, 1958-1962; nos. 54-84, 30 catalogs
    - Libreria Docet; Bologna (Box 414, Folder 2778-2779)
    - Libreria Docet; Bologna (Box 415, Folder 2780)
  - X346 D66, 1825; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - T. Dodd; Liverpool (Box 415, Folder 2781)
  - X346 D661, 1910-1918; nos. 1-27, 37 catalogs
    Name Variant: Robert H. Dodd
    - Dodd Livingston; New York (Box 415, Folder 2782-2785)